<idea-plugin>
    <id>io.github.umutcansu.FlavorAutocompletePlugin</id>

    <name>Android Flavor Autocomplete</name>

    <vendor url="https://github.com/umutcansu">Umut Cansu</vendor>

    <idea-version since-build="242" />

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>org.intellij.groovy</depends>
    <depends>org.jetbrains.kotlin</depends>
    <depends>org.jetbrains.plugins.gradle</depends>
    <depends>org.jetbrains.android</depends>

    <description><![CDATA[
        <h1>Android Flavor Autocomplete</h1>
        <p>Tired of mistyping product flavor names or switching to your build.gradle file just to remember them? This plugin is for you!</p>
        <p><b>Android Flavor Autocomplete</b> scans all modules in your project, finds every product flavor you have defined, and provides instant autocompletion suggestions within string literals.</p>

        <h2>Key Features:</h2>
        <ul>
            <li><b>Project-Wide Scanning:</b> Finds flavors from all Android modules, not just the one you are currently working in.</li>
            <li><b>Smart Suggestions:</b> Autocompletion works seamlessly inside string literals in both Kotlin (<code>.kt</code>) and Groovy (<code>.gradle</code>, <code>.gradle.kts</code>) files.</li>
            <li><b>Time-Saving:</b> Speeds up writing build scripts, tests, and application code that references product flavors.</li>
            <li><b>Error Prevention:</b> Avoids typos and runtime errors caused by incorrect flavor names.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            Simply start typing a flavor name inside a string, and the plugin will offer a list of all available flavors in your project. It is a simple but powerful tool for any developer working on a multi-flavor Android application.
        </p>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <ul>
            <li>Fixed binary compatibility with Android Studio Narwhal and newer.</li>
            <li>Removed upper version bound for broader IDE compatibility.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <completion.contributor
                language="Groovy"
                order="first"
                implementationClass="io.github.umutcansu.flavorautocompleteplugin.FlavorCompletionContributor"/>

        <completion.contributor
                language="kotlin"
                order="first"
                implementationClass="io.github.umutcansu.flavorautocompleteplugin.FlavorCompletionContributor"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>